{
  "categories": [],
  "description": " Answer these questions about the music of the 1980's. ",
  "difficulty": -1,
  "questions": [{
    "answer": "Ozzy Osbourne",
    "category": "1980's Music Trivia #2",
    "question": "Who bit the head off a bat?"
  }, {
    "answer": "Like a Virgin",
    "category": "1980's Music Trivia #2",
    "question": "What song was parodied by \"Like a Surgeon\"?"
  }, {
    "answer": "John Lennon",
    "category": "1980's Music Trivia #2",
    "question": "Who was shot by Mark David Chapman?"
  }, {
    "answer": "Billy Idol",
    "category": "1980's Music Trivia #2",
    "question": "What singer recorded \"White Wedding\"?"
  }, {
    "answer": "Born in the U.S.A.",
    "category": "1980's Music Trivia #2",
    "question": "What Bruce Springsteen song about a Vietnam vet is often mistaken for a patriotic anthem?"
  }, {
    "answer": "Jessie's",
    "category": "1980's Music Trivia #2",
    "question": "Whose girl did Rick Springfield wish he had?"
  }, {
    "answer": "Thriller",
    "category": "1980's Music Trivia #2",
    "question": "What was the best-selling album of the decade?"
  }, {
    "answer": "Top Gun",
    "category": "1980's Music Trivia #2",
    "question": "What movie featured the song \"Take My Breath Away\"?"
  }, {
    "answer": "Blondie",
    "category": "1980's Music Trivia #2",
    "question": "What new wave band did Debbie Harry sing for?"
  }, {
    "answer": "Physical",
    "category": "1980's Music Trivia #2",
    "question": "For what song did Olivia Newton-John film an exercise-themed video?"
  }, {
    "answer": "Runâ€“D.M.C.",
    "category": "1980's Music Trivia #2",
    "question": "What hip hop group covered the Aerosmith song \"Walk This Way\"?"
  }, {
    "answer": "Joan Jett's",
    "category": "1980's Music Trivia #2",
    "question": "Whose band was called \"The Blackhearts\"?"
  }, {
    "answer": "867-5309",
    "category": "1980's Music Trivia #2",
    "question": "What was Jenny's phone number?"
  }, {
    "answer": "Wang Chung",
    "category": "1980's Music Trivia #2",
    "question": "What group recorded \"Everybody Have Fun Tonight\"?"
  }, {
    "answer": "Lionel Richie",
    "category": "1980's Music Trivia #2",
    "question": "Who did Diana Ross sing a duet with in the song \"Endless Love\"?"
  }, {
    "answer": "Sammy Hagar",
    "category": "1980's Music Trivia #2",
    "question": "Who replaced David Lee Roth as the lead singer of Van Halen?"
  }, {
    "answer": "South Africa",
    "category": "1980's Music Trivia #2",
    "question": "To what country did Paul Simon travel to record his album \"Graceland\"?"
  }, {
    "answer": "The Power of Love",
    "category": "1980's Music Trivia #2",
    "question": "What Huey Lewis & The News song played at the beginning of \"Back to the Future\"?"
  }, {
    "answer": "Bon Scott",
    "category": "1980's Music Trivia #2",
    "question": "What AC/DC lead singer died of alcohol poisoning?"
  }, {
    "answer": "Public Enemy",
    "category": "1980's Music Trivia #2",
    "question": "What rap group urged listeners to \"Fight the Power\"?"
  }, {
    "answer": "Madonna",
    "category": "1980's Music Trivia #2",
    "question": "Who was the most successful female artist of th 80's"
  }, {
    "answer": "The Beastie Boys",
    "category": "1980's Music Trivia #2",
    "question": "Which three man rap duo sang 'Brass Monkey'"
  }, {
    "answer": "Another Brick in the wall",
    "category": "1980's Music Trivia #2",
    "question": "Pink Floyd's most popular song"
  }, {
    "answer": "Michael Jackson",
    "category": "1980's Music Trivia #2",
    "question": "Who had the highest number of top 100 hits in the 80's"
  }],
  "quizLength": 20,
  "title": "1980's Music Trivia #2",
  "url": "http://www.jetpunk.com/quizzes/1980s-music-trivia-2"
}
